http://www.linksvet.co.uk/cookie-policy

Contact Us
We are open and COVID-19 SECURE. Click here to find out more
Cookie Policy
About Cookies
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our website. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy below.
Your cookies have been updated
Thank you for updating your cookie settings.
Cookie settings
We use 3 different types of cookies on our website. You can say which ones you're happy for us to use below.
Functional cookies
These cookies do things like keep the website secure. They always need to be on.
Analytics cookies
These cookies store information about how you use our website, such as what you click on.
On
Off
Marketing cookies
These cookies do things like tell us if you've seen our adverts on social media, such as Facebook or Twitter.
On
Off
Update cookies
Uses made of the information
We use information held about you in the following ways:
Information you give to us. We will use this information:
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are a new visitor, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data (the contact form OR registration form);
to notify you about changes to our service;
to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer
Information we collect about you. We will use this information:
to administer our website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
to improve our website to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
as part of our efforts to keep our website safe and secure;
to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our website about goods or services that may interest you or them
Information we receive from other sources. We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).
Disclosure of your information
We may share your personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.
We may share your information with selected third parties including:
Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our website.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
If Independent Vetcare Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Independent Vetcare Limited, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff, operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things such as the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Independent Vetcare Limited will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data.  You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at: Independent Vetcare, The Chocolate Factory, Keynsham, Bristol, BS31 2AU. Email contact@independentvetcare.co.uk
Our website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Access to information
The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to:
Independent Vetcare, The Chocolate Factory, Keynsham, Bristol, BS31 2AU.
Fax: 01225 580077
Tel: 01225 481520
Email: contact@independentvetcare.co.uk
Our cookie policy
It is essential for the function of our site that we place a text file called a ‘cookie’ in the browser files of your computer when you visit. The cookie may be stored on your computer's hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly if you do.
We will not allow third parties to place cookies on our web site. Some third parties serve cookies on other sites that help us improve our service. For example, like most companies, we use Google Analytics to help us monitor our website traffic.
Back
About Us
Offers
Emergencies
Prices
Payment and Insurance
Client Charter
Feedback
